Guide to the Paula Green papers, 1940-2013 and undated RL.11500
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1959-2013 and undated; 6
  - ILGWU--Radio mix Chorus III, Undated (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-128)
  - ILGWU--Spanish, 1980 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-129)
  - ILGWU--Union Label :25 harmonica and guitar, Undated (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-130)
  - ILGWU--Union Label :25 harmonica and guitar, Undated (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-131)
  - ILGWU--Union Label :25 harmonica and guitar, Undated (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-132)
  - ILGWU--Union Label :25 harmonica and guitar, Undated (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-133)
  - ILGWU--Washington Veto #672, 1986 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-134)
  - ILGWU--Washington Veto #672, 1986 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-135)
  - ILGWU--We Make Jobs, 1992 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-136)
  - ILGWU--We Make Jobs, 1992 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-137)
  - ILGWU--We Make Jobs, 1992 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-138)
  - ILGWU--We Make Jobs, 1992 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-139)
  - ILGWU--We Make Jobs, 1992 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-140)
  - ILGWU--We Make Jobs, 1992 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-141)
  - ILGWU--We Make Jobs, 1992 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-142)
  - Jim Roach, 1972 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-143)
  - Jerusalem Post: Listening Post 681, Undated (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-144)
  - Jerusalem Post: Listening Post 681, Undated (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-145)
  - Life Extension Institute--Extraordinary Place #679, 1990 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-146)
  - Life Extension Institute--Extraordinary Place #679, 1990 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-147)
  - Life Extension Institute--Good Morning #675, 1988 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-148)
  - Life Extension Institute--Good Morning #675, 1988 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-149)
  - Life Extension Institute--Good Morning #675, 1988 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-150)
  - Life Extension Institute--Good Morning #675, 1988 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-151)
  - Life Extension Institute--Good Morning #675, 1988 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-152)
  - Life Extension Institute--Good Morning #675, 1988 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-153)
  - Life Extension Institute--Good Morning #675, 1988 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-154)
  - Marval Poultry--Arlen Dean Snyder: Pledge, Parts, 1981 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-155)
  - Marval Turkeys, Undated (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-156)
  - Music of Debussey, Undated (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-157)
  - New York Times 1, 1974 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-158)
    Margaret Mary; Arthur Daley; N.Y. Survey; Blue Collar; Tammy Grimes Stand By
  - New York Times 5: Tammy Grimes Uncertain World, Undated (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-159)
  - New York Times 6: New York Times Radio "Music", Undated (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-160)
  - New York Times 7: New York Times Radio #573, 1975 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-161)
  - New York Times 8: New York Times Radio spot, 1971 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-162)
  - New York Times 8: John O'Connor reel 1, Undated (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-163)
  - New York Times 8: John O'Connor reel 2, Undated (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-164)
  - New York Times 8: Master, Alan Truscott; Max Frankel; Bob Loggia, 1974 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-165)
  - New York Times 8: Spots, 1975 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-166)
    O'Connor "Ratings"; O'Connor "TV News"; Honan "Guide"; Honan "Artists"
  - New York Times 8: Bill Honan, Undated (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-167)
  - New York Times 8: New York Times Delivery, 1975 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-168)
  - New York Times 12: Spots, Undated (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-169)
    "LBJ" Ed Binns; Starting Sunday; Now Appearing
  - New York Times 18: 15 spots, 1973 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-170)
  - New York Times 18: New York Times Delivery, 1975 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-171)
  - New York Times 19: Radio reel 14 spots, 1971 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-172)
  - New York Times 21: Spots, 1975 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-173)
  - New York Times 22: Sports, 1972 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-174)
    Pearl Bailey; Mets Radio Sign Man; Football Training Camp; Football Player; Dave Anderson
  - New York Times 24: Home Delivery, Undated (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-175)
    Suburban Housewife; Business Man; Working Woman; Blue Collar
  - New York Times 080: Spots, Undated (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-176)
    Blue Collar; Clive Barnes Black Theatre; Oysters (Female); Tammy Grimes Bright and Shiny; Kelly
  - New York Times 294A: Suburban Housewife; Businessman, 1975 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-177)
  - New York Times 336: 800 3 voices; Brooks 800, 1975 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-178)
  - New York Times 336: New York Times Delivery :60, 1975 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-179)
  - New York Times 573: Home Delivery, 1975 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-180)
  - New York Times A: Umbrella, Undated (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-181)
    Max Frankel III; John Leonard 2000 Books
  - New York Times: Ada Louise Huxtable, Undated (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-182)
  - New York Times B: Home Delivery, Undated (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-183)
    Serious Music; Suburban Housewife
  - New York Times BB: 800 3 voices; Brooks 800, 1975 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-184)
  - New York Times C: Content and Special, Undated (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-185)
    New York Survey; Oysters; Problems
  - New York Times--Clive Barnes III, 1974 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-186)
  - New York Times--Demo reel, Undated (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-187)
  - New York Times--Detroit New Promotion, Undated (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-188)
    Pearl Bailey; Buddy Hackett; Suburban Housewife; Business Man; Working Woman; Blue Collar; Double Decker Bus; Oysters
  - New York Times--Festival of Music: Truscott; Frankel, Undated (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-189)
  - New York Times--Home Delivery, 1976 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-190)
  - New York Times--Home Delivery, Undated (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-191)
  - New York Times--Home Delivery: Serious Music with Man and Woman, 1975 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-192)
  - New York Times--John Canady interview, 1972 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-193)
  - New York Times--John Leonard, 1974 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-194)
  - New York Times--John O'Connor reel 2, Undated (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-195)
  - New York Times--N.Y. Times Revised, 1975 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-196)
  - New York Times--Radio: Tom Mullaney, 1972 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-197)
  - New York Times--Radio reel 14 spots, 1971 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-198)
  - New York Times--Spots, Undated (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-199)
    Organist; Tuba; Conductor
  - New York Times--Spots, 1974 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-200)
    Talking to Your Plants; Dear Joan Faust; Spring Has Sprung; The Move to the Suburbs; Alan Truscott
  - New York Times--Vincent Canby interview reel 1, 1973 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-201)
  - New York Times--Vincent Canby interview reel 2, 1973 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-202)
  - New York Times--Will Weng, 1972 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-203)
  - New York Times--Tammy Grimes Bright and Shiny, Undated (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-204)
  - New York Times--Tammy Grimes Bright and Shiny, Undated (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-205)
  - New York Times--Tammy Grimes Bright and Shiny, Undated (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-206)
  - New York Times--Tammy Grimes Uncertain World, 1975 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-207)
  - New York Times--Tammy Grimes Who's Afraid, Undated (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-208)
  - Sound Effects: Applause, large, Undated (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-209)
  - Sound Effects: Running Steps, Undated (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-210)
  - State of Israel Bonds, 1991 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-211)
  - State of Israel Bonds, WINS, 1992 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-212)
  - Sterling Bank #680, 1990 (Box AV33, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-213)
  - Sterling Bank #680, 1990 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-214)
  - Sterling Bank #680, 1990 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-215)
  - Sterling Bank #680, 1990 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-216)
  - Sterling Bank #680, 1990 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-217)
  - Sterling Bank #680, 1990 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-218)
  - Sterling Bank #680, 1990 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-219)
  - Sterling Bank #680, 1990 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-220)
  - Sterling Bank #677 60th Anniversary, Undated (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-221)
  - Sterling Bank #677 60th Anniversary, Undated (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-222)
  - Sterling Bank #658 Doors, Undated (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-223)
  - Sterling Bank #658 Doors, Undated (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-224)
  - Sterling Bank #658 Doors, Undated (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-225)
  - Sterling Bank #658 Doors, Undated (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-226)
  - Sterling Bank #658 Doors, Undated (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-227)
  - Sterling Bank #658 Doors, 1981 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-228)
  - Sterling Bank #658 Doors, 1981 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-229)
  - Sterling Bank #658 Doors, 1982 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-230)
  - Sterling Bank Doors roll 1, 1981 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-231)
  - Sterling Bank Doors roll 2, 181 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-232)
  - Sterling Bank Doors roll 3, 1981 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-233)
  - Sterling Bank Doors roll 4, 1981 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-234)
  - Sterling Bank #688 Hometown, 1993 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-235)
  - Sterling Bank #688 Hometown, 1993 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-236)
  - Sterling Bank #688 Hometown, 1993 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-237)
  - Sterling Bank #689 Hometown II, 1993 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-238)
  - Sterling Bank #689 Hometown II, 1993 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-239)
  - Sterling Bank #689 Hometown II, 1993 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-240)
  - Sterling Bank--I Wouldn't Have It Any Other Way, Undated (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-241)
  - Sterling Bank--Member FDIC, 1989 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-242)
  - Sterling Bank #680 Money to Lend, 1990 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-243)
  - Sterling Bank #670 Substantial Business, 1986 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-244)
  - Sterling Bank #674 Substantial Business II, Undated (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-245)
  - Sterling Bank #674 Substantial Business II, Undated (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-246)
  - Sterling Bank #674 Substantial Business II, Undated (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-247)
  - Sterling Bank #674 Substantial Business II, Undated (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-248)
  - Sterling Bank #674 Substantial Business II, Undated (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-249)
  - Sterling Bank #674 Substantial Business II, Undated (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-250)
  - Subaru--Ask Me Why, Undated (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-251)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 4: Mila, Nina take 16, Undated (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-252)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 5: Young Girl (Brianna); Gonna Tell You Something, 1973 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-253)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 6: 6 spots, 1973 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-254)
    William; 1,2,3; Hayseed; Reading; The Cigarette World
  - U.S. Public Health Service 7: Presentation 9 spots, 1973 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-255)
    Zohra Lampert; Barbara Speilberg; Geraldine Fitzgerald; Scorecard; Young Man Old Man; Young Woman; Gonna Tell You Something; Her Automatic Cigarette
  - U.S. Public Health Service spots, 1973 (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-256)
  - U.S. Public Health Service--Women and Smoking, Undated (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-257)
    Zohra Lampert; Barbara Speilberg; Geraldine Fitzgerald; Bob Loggia
  - New York Post: Racing Extra :60, Undated (Box AV34, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-258)
  - 7490. Goya--Effects master, Undated (Box AV35, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-001)
  - 7492. Goya--Spots, 1983 (Box AV35, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-002)
  - 7493. Goya--Audio elements for mix, 1983 (Box AV35, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-003)
  - 7495. Goya--New Beans not for air, 1985 (Box AV35, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-004)
  - 7496. Goya--New Beans :30, 1985 (Box AV35, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-005)
  - 7497. Goya--New Beans not for air, 1985 (Box AV35, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-006)
  - 7503. Goya--Product shots, 1985 (Box AV35, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-007)
  - 7521. Goya--Sazon :30, 1985 (Box AV35, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-008)
  - Goya--Can opening demo, Undated (Box AV35, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-009)
  - Goya--Edit element, Undated (Box AV35, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-010)
  - Goya--Spots, 1983 (Box AV35, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-011)
  - Goya--Salad Toss revised, 1984 (Box AV35, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-012)
  - Goya--Sazon, 1985 (Box AV35, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-013)
  - Goya--19 spots, 1987 (Box AV35, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-014)
  - ILGWU--Barbees :60, 1987 (Box AV35, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-015)
  - ILGWU--Dub reel 101, 1991 (Box AV35, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-016)
  - ILGWU--5 spots, 1982 (Box AV36, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-017)
    Emma retired worker; Jim Prine II; Norma II outdoor; Bledsoes with chorus; Song We Sing
  - ILGWU--Health Care :30, 1994 (Box AV36, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-018)
  - ILGWU--Health Care :30, 1994 (Box AV36, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-019)
  - ILGWU--Health Care :30 master, 1994 (Box AV36, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-020)
  - ILGWU--Health Care :30 protection, 1994 (Box AV36, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-021)
  - ILGWU--Health Care :30 protection, 1994 (Box AV36, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-022)
  - ILGWU--Lydia :60, 1987 (Box AV36, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-023)
  - ILGWU--Meredith :60, 1987 (Box AV36, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-024)
  - ILGWU--Multi-Shop :30, 1988 (Box AV36, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-025)
  - ILGWU--Multi-Shop Join In :30, 1988 (Box AV36, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-026)
  - ILGWU--Multi-Shop Join In :30 protection master, 1988 (Box AV36, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-027)
  - ILGWU--On Stage :30, 1990 (Box AV36, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-028)
  - ILGWU--On Stage II :30, 1991 (Box AV36, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-029)
  - ILGWU--Protection Multi, Undated (Box AV36, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-030)
  - ILGWU--Song We Sing, 1982 (Box AV36, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-031)
  - ILGWU--Statue :30, 1986 (Box AV36, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-032)
  - ILGWU--Statue :30, 1986 (Box AV37, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-033)
  - ILGWU--Statue :30, 1986 (Box AV37, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-034)
  - ILGWU--Statue :30, 1986 (Box AV37, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-035)
  - ILGWU--Statue :30, 1986 (Box AV37, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-036)
  - ILGWU--Statue :30, 1986 (Box AV37, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-037)
  - ILGWU--Spots, 1991 (Box AV37, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-038)
    Susan; Judy and Jamin; Ramona
  - ILGWU--Spots, 1991 (Box AV37, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-039)
  - ILGWU--Spots, 1991 (Box AV37, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-040)
  - ILGWU--Spots, 1991 (Box AV37, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-041)
  - ILGWU--Spots, 1991 (Box AV37, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-042)
  - ILGWU--Voting :30, 1986 (Box AV37, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-043)
  - ILGWU--Voting :30, 1986 (Box AV37, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-044)
  - ILGWU--We Make Jobs, 1992 (Box AV37, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-045)
  - ILGWU--We Make Jobs, 1992 (Box AV37, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-046)
  - ILGWU--We Make Jobs, 1992 (Box AV37, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-047)
  - ILGWU--We Make Jobs, 1992 (Box AV37, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-048)
  - ILGWU--We Make Jobs, 1992 (Box AV38, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-049)
  - ILGWU--We Make Jobs, 1992 (Box AV38, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-050)
  - ILGWU--YGW-0157 without music, Undated (Box AV38, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-051)
  - Marval Turkeys, 1982 (Box AV38, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-052)
    I Do, I Do; Pledge; Parts
  - WLR 13:00, Undated (Box AV38, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-053)
  - ILGWU--Spots, 1982 (Box AV38, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-054)
    Americans Helping Americans; Clothes in Your Closet; A Little American Flag: Beverly; Kathy; Joan
  - Sterling Bank: 8 tracks, 1981 (Box AV38, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-055)
  - New York Times--8 tracks, 1977 (Box AV39, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-056)
  - ILGWU--Dub reel 100, 1991 (Box AV39, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-057)
  - Goya--Bean Book :30, Undated (Box AV39, Video-reel RL11500-VID1-058)
  - Goya--Bean Book :30, 1980 (Box AV38, Video-reel RL11500-VID2-001)
  - Marval Turkeys--Breakaway :30, 1979 (Box AV38, Video-reel RL11500-VID2-002)
  - Marval Turkeys--Elegant Table :30, 1979 (Box AV38, Video-reel RL11500-VID2-003)
  - Marval Turkeys--Now's the Time :30, Undated (Box AV38, Video-reel RL11500-VID2-004)
  - Marval Turkeys--Charts, 1979 (Box AV39, Video-reel RL11500-VID2-005)
  - ILGWU 1--parodies, Undated (Box AV39, Video-cassette RL11500-FS8-001)
  - ILGWU 2--Commercials, Undated (Box AV40, Video-cassette RL11500-FS8-002)
  - ILGWU 3--parodies, Undated (Box AV40, Video-cassette RL11500-FS8-003)
  - Marval Turkeys 1, Undated (Box AV40, Video-cassette RL11500-FS8-004)
  - Marval Turkeys 2, Undated (Box AV40, Video-cassette RL11500-FS8-005)
  - Marval Turkeys 3--Talking BBQ, Undated (Box AV40, Video-cassette RL11500-FS8-006)
  - Marval Turkeys 8--Fairchild Presentation, 1982 (Box AV40, Video-cassette RL11500-FS8-007)
  - Marval Turkeys 9--Fairchild Presentation, 1982 (Box AV40, Video-cassette RL11500-FS8-008)
  - Paramount Poultry 1, Undated (Box AV40, Video-cassette RL11500-FS8-009)
  - Marval Turkeys 10--Summertime/Turkey, Undated (Box AV40, Video-cassette RL11500-FS8-010)
  - Paramount Poultry 2, Undated (Box AV40, Video-cassette RL11500-FS8-011)
  - Paramount Poultry 3, Undated (Box AV40, Video-cassette RL11500-FS8-012)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 1--Automatic Cigarette, Undated (Box AV40, Video-cassette RL11500-FS8-013)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 2--Automatic Cigarette, Undated (Box AV40, Video-cassette RL11500-FS8-014)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 3, Undated (Box AV40, Video-cassette RL11500-FS8-015)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 4, Undated (Box AV40, Video-cassette RL11500-FS8-016)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 5: Bad Is Better Than Worse, Undated (Box AV40, Video-cassette RL11500-FS8-017)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 6: Bad Is Better Than Worse, Undated (Box AV40, Video-cassette RL11500-FS8-018)
  - ILGWU 4--Commercials and parodies, Undated (Box AV40, Video-cassette RL11500-FS8-019)
  - ILGWU 5--Commercials and parodies, Undated (Box AV40, Video-cassette RL11500-FS8-020)
  - American Cancer Society 27--The Technique of Breast Self Examination :60, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-001)
  - American Cancer Society 28--PAP Test (in Spanish) Little Girl with local phone number :30, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-002)
  - American Cancer Society--Tammy Grimes Breast Self Examination :60, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-003)
  - American Cancer Society--Uterine Cancer spot "Little Girl" :60, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-004)
  - American Cancer Society--Uterine Cancer spot "Little Girl" :60, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-005)
  - New York Times 4--Op Ed, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-006)
  - New York Times 5--Op Ed, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-007)
  - New York Times 23--Armand Frankel, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-008)
  - New York Times--Audrey Jones :30, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-009)
  - New York Times--Bouncing Ball :30, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-010)
  - New York Times--Bouncing Ball :30, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-011)
  - New York Times--Bouncing Ball :30, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-012)
  - New York Times--Bouncing Ball :30, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-013)
  - New York Times--F. Genovese :30, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-014)
  - New York Times--Home Delivery "Door" original :10, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-015)
  - New York Times--Jim Mayor :30, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-016)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 11--Women and Smoking :20, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-017)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 12--Women and Smoking :20, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-018)
  - American Cancer Society 32--Nina, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-019)
  - ILGWU 20--American Dope Growers, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-020)
  - New York Times--Home Delivery "Door" original :10, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-021)
  - New York Times 2--Op Ed, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-022)
  - New York Times 3--Op Ed, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-023)
  - New York Times 6--Untitled, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-024)
  - New York Times 12--Bob Nolo, Jerome Langed, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-025)
  - New York Times 14--Sports: Red Smith, Art Daly, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-026)
  - New York Times 22, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-027)
    Billy Graham on Lt. Calley; Home Delivery
  - Paramount Poultry 1, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-028)
    Pearlie's Kitchen; Mama's Kitchen
  - Paramount Poultry 2, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-029)
  - Paramount Poultry, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-030)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 3--Cigarette World, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-031)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 4--Lots of Good Reasons :60, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-032)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 5--Zohra "We've Come a Long Way Baby", Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-033)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 6--Lots of Good Reasons :60, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-034)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 7--Zohra "We've Come a Long Way Baby", Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-035)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 13--Automatic Cigarette, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-036)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 33--Smoke Watch :30, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-037)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 33--Smoke Watch :30, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-038)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 34--Smoke Watch :30, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-039)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 34--Smoke Watch :30, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-040)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 35--Women and Smoking :30, Undated (Box AV41, Film-reel RL11500-F16-041)
  - American Cancer Society--Lola Falana, 1976 (Box AV42, Film-reel RL11500-F16-042)
  - ILGWU reel 2, 1978 (Box AV42, Film-reel RL11500-F16-043)
    Lillian; Emma; Grandmother/Granddaughter; Barbees; Bledsoes; Meredith/Outdoor chorus; Lydia/Indoor chorus; Jim Prine/Indoor chorus
  - ILGWU 18, Undated (Box AV42, Film-reel RL11500-F16-044)
    Jim Prine; Emma; Donnie & Marie; Merv Griffin; Saturday Nite Live
  - ILGWU 19--Carol Burnett parody, Undated (Box AV42, Film-reel RL11500-F16-045)
  - New York Times 7--14 spots, 1971 (Box AV42, Film-reel RL11500-F16-046)
  - New York Times 15--Plumber, Harpist, Squash; Ballet, Undated (Box AV42, Film-reel RL11500-F16-047)
  - New York Times 16--January sample reel, 1974 (Box AV42, Film-reel RL11500-F16-048)
  - New York Times 17, Undated (Box AV42, Film-reel RL11500-F16-049)
  - New York Times 19, Undated (Box AV42, Film-reel RL11500-F16-050)
    Sports; Nixon in China; Whirling Ball; Wall St.; Bouncing Ball
  - New York Times 20, Undated (Box AV42, Film-reel RL11500-F16-051)
    Readers of the Times; Home Delivery; Ada Louise; Op Ed
  - New York Times 24, Undated (Box AV42, Film-reel RL11500-F16-052)
  - New York Times 25--14 spots, 1971 (Box AV42, Film-reel RL11500-F16-053)